2014 beginning of 2014 they call
2014 principio del 2014 llaman a la
Jaime Peñafiel to the editorial office of the world, a
redacción del mundo a Jaime peñafiel una
lady from Mexico, specifically
señora desde México en concreto
Guadalajara. This lady introduces herself as
Guadalajara esta señora se presenta como
the wife of a well-known director of a
la esposa de un conocido director de un
Mexican media outlet. This
medio de comunicación mexicano esta
lady tells Jaime Peña Fiel that
señora le cuenta a Jaime Peña fiel que
her husband had an affair in the past with
su marido en el pasado se enrollo con
a 23-year-old girl. He was 11 years
una chica de 23 años él tenía 11 años
older than her, he was 34. Apparently, he got
más él tenía 34 él por lo visto se
hooked. He got so hooked that Leticia,
enganchó se enganchó tanto que Leticia
after
después de haberse estado teniendo este
supposedly having this affair with this gentleman,
romance supuestamente con este caballero
went to Spain. He returned to Spain and the
se fue a España se volvió a España y el
man was left crying. He was
hombre se quedó llorando se quedó
completely heartbroken because
completamente desconsolado porque se
this lady had left. And then, after a while, he
había ido esta señora y luego al tiempo
finds out that the girl who
se encuentra con que esa chica que la
had driven him crazy was now the Queen of
había vuelto loco ahora era la reina de
Spain. And he had a wife and five
España y esto él teniendo mujer y cinco
children.
hijos